Guide to the Bulldogs Across America, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Bulldogs Across America, Yale College, records
1999-2012
RU 1125
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1
(2 boxes)
This collection consists of administrative records of Bulldogs Across America, an alumni-sponsored summer internship progrma for Yale students. The records include newpaper and magazine articles about the program, agreements with local programs and Yale University, correspondence, financial information, and electronic records.
Yale University. Bulldogs Across America
Biographical / Historical
Bulldogs Across America, founded in 1999, is a program for Yale undergraduate students that provides alumni-sponsored summer internships in several different cities around the United States. The program offers students work experience in both the for-profit and non-profit sectors, networking and educational opportunities, and mentorship from Yale alumni.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of administrative records of Bulldogs Across America including newpaper and magazine articles about the program, agreements with local programs and Yale University, correspondence, financial information, and electronic records.
Arrangement
The records are arranged as received.
Conditions Governing Access
Access prohibited for 35 years from creation of the records.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
General
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-E (YRG 9-E), Records documenting Yale College offices, programs, and projects.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of John Rowan Claypool V, 2013
Internship programs -- Connecticut -- New Haven; Yale University -- Students; Yale University -- Undergraduates; Yale University. Bulldogs Across America
- Records, Accession 2013-A-058
  - Correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Subject files
    - General
      - 1999-2008 (Box 1, Folder 2-11)
      - 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 1-4)
      - 2012 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Bulldogs in the Bluegrass archives, 1999-2004 (Box 2, Folder 6-9)
    - Bulldogs Across America website documentation, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Electronic records (Reel 3)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.